https://www.tour-maidstone.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy | Tour Maidstone
HomeAboutBlogCategoriesBusinessHealthTravellingHome Improvement ToolsContact
Twitter
Facebook
Instagram
Pinterest
Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy of Tour-Maidstone.comYour PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART CookieGoogle, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies,Tour Maidstone has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.Collection of Personal InformationWhen visiting Tour Maidstone, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.Links to third party WebsitesWe have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.Changes to this Privacy StatementThe contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Tour Maidstone then you may contact us at info@tour-maidstone.com
SearchAbout MeHi, I am Carl C. Locke born in England. I run this tour-maidstone website. I am a passionate travel blogger. But i also love to write about home improvement and recent topics.I am married and lived a happily married life with my beautiful wife. We have 2 daughters and one son.Hope, you will enjoy this blog.CategoriesBusinessGift IdeasHealthHome Improvement ToolsTravellingRecent PostsWhat is Mechanics Tool sets and How to Use it?November 4, 2018How To Get Rid Of Pesky Weeds In Your Lawn Using A String TrimmerJune 1, 2018Is It Safe To Use Scratch Nonstick Pan?June 1, 2018What is Mechanics Tool sets and How to Use it?November 4, 2018Maidstone Borough Council is part of the Heart of Kent ConsortiumJune 12, 2015Archbishops PalaceNovember 9, 2017What is Mechanics Tool sets and How to Use it?November 4, 2018How To Get Rid Of Pesky Weeds In Your Lawn Using A String TrimmerJune 1, 2018Is It Safe To Use Scratch Nonstick Pan?June 1, 2018 christmas christmas gift for kids electric griddle electric meat grinders emotional freedom gift ideas heal dry facial skin home remedies maidstone maidstone borough council micro businesses for teenagers Nonstick Pan string trimmer sunmile electric meat grinder SM-G50 wedding portrait photographerVisit LondonRandom PostsGood Christmas Gift Ideas For Kids 2018Getting to MaidstoneSimple and Effective Steps to Emotional FreedomVisit LondonPopular PostsWhat is Mechanics Tool sets and How to Use it?November 4, 2018Maidstone Borough Council is part of the Heart of Kent ConsortiumJune 12, 2015Archbishops PalaceNovember 9, 2017 © 2017 By Tour-Maidstone | Home | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer | Sitemap Back To Top
